

# TRAN KIEU ANH

BANKER AND RISK SPECIALIST

Female

27.10.1992

093.464.4306

kieuanhtran271092@gmail.com

② Linkedin.com/ in/ anh.trankieu.com

• Hoang Mai Hanoi Vietnam

### **SKILLS**

#### Language:

English, Vietnamese

#### Computer:

Word, Excel, Powerpoint

## **HONORS & AWARDS**

**2021**: CVEC scholarship of Audencia Business School

**2021**: Top 10 excellent students of CFVG in first year

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

2015: British Council IELTS 7.0

**2020**: IIG Academy TOEIC 940/990

## **INTERESTS**

Forex, Stocks and Blockchain.

### **OBJECTIVE**

Take advantages of banking experiences and risks control in operations to become a professional researcher in banking and related organizations and bring values to organizations I work for. From then, I will become a specialist in finance and related services in the future.

### **EDUCATION**

#### **National Economics University**

Banking and Finance

August 2011 - June 2015

GPA 8.0/10

#### Centre Franco-Vietnamien de formation à la Gestion

MBA September 2019 - September 2021

#### **Audencia Business School**

International Master of Management Sep

September 2020 - November 2021

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Bank for Investment and Development of Vietnam**

Teller and Risk control specialist

2017 - now

- Daily tracking, recording, reporting, and storing information related to transactions, cards and remittance ensuring all information is accurate and complete.
- Report on risks emerging from bank processing procedures.
- Build up the model for calculating risk of money flow in banking system.
- Monthly report on risk activities in daily operations related to Basel II accord.
- Monthly report on risk classification of credit in branch.
- Dealing with daily customer services and keep update the account management of customersl

#### Ladofoods

Logistics assistant

2015 - 2016

Making accounting report about the risk emerging from logistics activities.

## **REFERENCES**

KAPITSKAIA Olga okapitskaia@audencia.com Tran Van Thang Thangtv@Ladofoods.com.vn

# **ACTIVITIES**

## Vietnam Buddhist Sangha

Assistant 2014 -

Contribution to Buddha Purina and Buddha Day in Vietnam.

#### **REACH SE**

Teaching assistant 2014 -

Volunteer English Teaching program